Finding Aid for the The Francis Robinson Collection
Special Collections and University Archives
- (The File Description)
  - Robinson Photograph Collection (Stu - Tw)
    - La Traviata (Box 93, Folder 43)
    - Trevesan, Vitlorio (Box 93, Folder 44)
    - Tristan and Isolde (Box 93, Folder 45)
    - Il Trovatore (Box 93, Folder 46)
    - Tucci, Gabriella (Box 93, Folder 47)
    - Tucker, Richard (Box 93, Folder 48)
    - Tunney, Gene (Box 93, Folder 49)
    - Turner, Dame Eva (Box 93, Folder 50)
    - Two on an Island (Box 93, Folder 51)
  - Robinson Photograph Collection (Up - Zi)
    - Uppman, Theodore (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Valentive, Mary (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Valentino, Francesco (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Valentino, Rudolf (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Valletti, Cesare (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Vanderbilt University (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Vanderbilt Board of Trust (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Vanderbilt Singers (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Van Patten, Diekie (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Varden, Evelyn (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Varviso, Silvio (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Vass, Lt. S. (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Vaughan, Gene, Susan, Margaret, Richard (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - Velis, Andrea (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - Verchinina, Nina and Zoritch, Georges (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - Verdi, Casa (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - Vichegonov, Lubomir (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - Vickers, Jon Family (Box 94, Folder 18)
    - Wagner, Charles L. (Box 94, Folder 19)
    - Wagner, Cosima (Box 94, Folder 20)
    - Walker, Marci and Family (Box 94, Folder 21)
    - Walker, William (Box 94, Folder 22)
    - Die Walkur (Box 94, Folder 23)
    - Walindander, Joan (Box 94, Folder 24)
    - Walthall, Henry B. (Box 94, Folder 25)
    - Waring, Fred (Box 94, Folder 26)
    - Wane, Michael (Box 94, Folder 27)
    - Warren, Leonard (Box 94, Folder 28)
    - Waters, Bedford (Box 94, Folder 29)
    - Waters, Ethel (Box 94, Folder 30)
    - Weaver Brothers and Elivry (Box 94, Folder 31)
    - Weingartner, Felix V. (Box 94, Folder 32)
    - Weissmuller, Johnny (Box 94, Folder 33)
    - Welitsch, Ljuba (Box 94, Folder 34)
    - Werthor (Box 94, Folder 35)
    - West, Mae (Box 94, Folder 36)
    - Westmore, Ern (Box 94, Folder 37)
    - White, Lasses (Box 94, Folder 38)
    - White, Robert (Box 94, Folder 39)
    - Whiteman, Paul (Box 94, Folder 40)
    - Whitty, Dame May (Box 94, Folder 41)
    - Wickman and Family (Box 94, Folder 42)
    - Wildermann, William (Box 94, Folder 43)
    - Winninger, Charles (Box 94, Folder 44)
    - Winters, Johnny (Box 94, Folder 45)
    - Witherspoon, Herbert (Box 94, Folder 46)
    - Wood, Helen (Box 94, Folder 47)
    - Woollcott, Alexander (Box 94, Folder 48)
    - Woolley, Monty (Box 94, Folder 49)
    - Wright, Arthur (Box 94, Folder 50)
    - WSM (Box 94, Folder 51)
    - Wynn, Keenan (Box 94, Folder 52)
    - Yergin, Sonja (Box 94, Folder 53)
    - Yntema, Theodore (Box 94, Folder 54)
    - Yorke, Bob (Box 94, Folder 55)
    - Zalken, William (Box 94, Folder 56)
    - Die Zauber Flote (Box 94, Folder 57)
    - Zelzer, Harry (Box 94, Folder 58)
    - Zimbailist, Efrem (Box 94, Folder 59)
    - Zorina, Vera (Box 94, Folder 60)
  - Photographs - Unidentified
  - Photographs - Negatives
  - Photographs - Artists
    - Albanese, Licia (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Anderson, Judith (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Anderson, Judith and others (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Anderson, Marxwell (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Autry, Gene (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Bankhead, Talulah (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Barrymore, Ethel (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Bernstein, Leonard (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Boda, Bob (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Boyer, Charles & Fenwick, Jean (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Burrell, John (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Carlisle, Margaret (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - Cornell, Katharine and others (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Douglas, Kirk (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - Dunne, Eithre (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - Eddy, Nelson with Eleanor Powell and Jenneth MacDonald (Box 97, Folder 16)
    - Fassnacht, George Sr. (Box 97, Folder 17)
    - Fay, Vivien (Box 97, Folder 18)
    - Fitzsimmons, Foster (Box 97, Folder 19)
    - Fontanne, Lynn and Alfred Lunt (Box 97, Folder 20)
    - Garbo, Greta (Box 97, Folder 21)
    - Galli-Curci, Amelita (Box 97, Folder 22)
    - The-Girl of the Glden West (Box 97, Folder 23)
    - The Great Waltz (Box 97, Folder 24)
    - Hinkle, Carl (Box 97, Folder 25)
    - Hopkins, Miriam (Box 97, Folder 26)
    - Kelly, Pete (Box 97, Folder 27)
    - Kerrigan, J. M. (Box 97, Folder 28)
    - King Richard II (Box 97, Folder 29)
    - Koussevitzky, Serge and the Boston Symphony Orchestra (Box 97, Folder 30)
    - Levy, Ethel (Box 97, Folder 31)
    - Lord, Pauline (Box 97, Folder 32)
    - Losch, Tilly (Box 97, Folder 33)
    - McClintic, Guthrie (Box 97, Folder 34)
    - McCormilk, Myron and Stuart, James (Box 97, Folder 35)
    - Massey, Raymond (Box 97, Folder 36)
    - Mevedith, Burgess (Box 97, Folder 37)
    - Muni, Paul (Box 97, Folder 38)
    - Oliver, Laurence (Box 97, Folder 39)
    - Rathbone, Basil (Box 97, Folder 40)
    - Robinson, Francis (Box 97, Folder 41)
    - Rorem, Ned (Box 97, Folder 42)
    - Meck, Donald, Shaw, Oscar (Box 97, Folder 43)
    - Skinner, Cornelia Otis (Box 97, Folder 44)
    - Skinner, Otis (Box 97, Folder 45)
    - Stevens, Rise (Box 97, Folder 46)
    - The Student Prince (Box 97, Folder 47)
    - Tanglewood Festival (Box 97, Folder 48)
    - Toscanini, Arturo (Box 97, Folder 49)
    - Tucher, Richard (Box 97, Folder 50)
    - Verona, Italy (Box 97, Folder 51)
    - Verdi, Givseppe (Box 97, Folder 52)
    - Whiteman, Paul (Box 97, Folder 53)
    - Wnidentified (Box 97, Folder 54)
  - Prints
    - Jenny Lind (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Singers (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Violinists (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Composers (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Theatre People (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Theatre Scenes (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Opera Scenes (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Faust (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Theatre, Opera House (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Old Theatre and Opera Programs (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - Wagner (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Playbills (1)
    - 19th Century 1920 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - 1920's (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Alvin Theatre (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Aldwych Theatre (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Ambassador Theatre (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - American Theatre (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - American Shakespeare Festival Theatre (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - ANT Theatre and Ziegfield Theatre (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Ethel Barrymore Theatre (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Martin Beck Theatre (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Playbills (2)
    - Belasco Theatre (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Bijou Theatre (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Biltmore Theatre (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Blackstone Theatre (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - The Booth Theatre (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Boston Opera House (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Boston Theatre (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - The Broadhurst Theatre (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Broadway Theatre (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Cape Playhouse (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Cass Theatre and Cassino Theatre (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Cedarhurst Playhouse (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - Chestnut Street Opera House (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - Chicago Stagebill (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - Circle in the Square Theatre (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - Civic Auditorium, San Francisco (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - George M. Cohan Theatre (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - Coronet Theatre (Box 100, Folder 18)
    - Coronet Theatre (Box 100, Folder 19)
    - Cort Theatre (Box 100, Folder 20)
    - Court Square Theatre (Box 100, Folder 21)
    - Curren Theatre (Box 100, Folder 22)
    - Delacorte Theatre & Delaware Instituition Playhouse (Box 100, Folder 23)
    - Maxine Elliott's Theatre (Box 100, Folder 24)
  - Playbills (3)
    - The Empire Theatre (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - English Theatre & Evergreen Showcard (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Erlanger Theatre (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Ford's Theatre & Forrest Theatre (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - 51st Street, 41st Street, & 48th Street Theatres (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - 46th Street Theatre (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Geary Theatre & Tyrone Guthrie Theatre (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - The Guild Theatre (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Hanna, Hartman, Harvard & Holiday Theatres (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Helen Hayes Theatre (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Mark Hellenger Theatre (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Hudson Theatre (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - International Theatre & Alumni Memorial Auditorium (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - Imperial Theatre (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - Library & Museum of the Performing Arts, Loew's Theatre, & Lyric Theatre (Box 101, Folder 15)
    - Lyceum Theatre (Box 101, Folder 16)
    - Martinique Theatre, Maryland Theatre, Metropolitan Opera House; Metropolitan Theatre, Henry Miller's Theatre, Masque Theatre (Box 101, Folder 17)
    - The Majestic Theatre (Box 101, Folder 18)
  - Playbills (4)
    - Morosco Theatre (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - The Music Box Theatre (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - National Theatre (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - New Century Theatre (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - New York City Center of Music and Drama (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - New York State Theatre (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - North Shore Players (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Old Vic Theatre (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Eugene O'Neill Theatre, Opera House of Brooklyn Academy of Music (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Palace Theatre, the Playhouse, Promendade Theatre, the Provincetown Playhouse (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - The Playgoer (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Phoenix Theatre (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - Playbills (5)
    - Plymouth Theatre (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Billy Rose Theatre (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Royale Theatre (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Ryman Auditorium (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Savoy Theatre, Shubert Theatre (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - St. James Plymouth Theatre (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Wilbur Theatre, Willard Roof Music Hall, Wyndham's Theatre (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Winter Garden (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Ziegfeld Theatre (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Playbills (6)
    - A (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - B (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - C (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - D (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - E (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - F (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - G (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - H (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - I (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - J (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - K (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Playbills (7)
    - L (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - M (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - N (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - 0 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - R (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - S (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - T (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - U (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Playbills (8)
    - V (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - W (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Y (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Z (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Home to Shakespeare, As You Like It (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Hamlet (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Henry IV, Henry V (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Juliu Caesar, King Richard II (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - MacBeth (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - Othello, Romeo and Juliet (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - The Taming of the Shrew, Troilus & Cressida, Twelfth Night (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - Performers (1)
    - Adams, Maude - Biography (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Adams, Maude - Roles (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Adams, Maude - Roles (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Adams, Maude - Commemorative Booklets (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Anderson, Judith - Biography (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Anderson, Judith - Roles (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Anderson, Judith - Roles (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Anderson, Judith - Roles (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Bankhead, Tallulah - Biography (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Bankhead, Tallulah - Critiques (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Bankhead, Tallulah - Roles (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - Bankhead, Tallulah - Roles (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - Bankhead, Tallulah - Roles (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - Bankhead, Tallulah - Roles (Box 107, Folder 14)
    - Bankhead, Tallulah - Commemorative Booklets (Box 107, Folder 15)
    - Barrymore, Ethel - Biography (Box 107, Folder 16)
    - Barrymore, Ethel - Critiques (Box 107, Folder 17)
    - Barrymore, Ethel - Roles (Box 107, Folder 18)
    - Barrymore, Ethel - Roles (Box 107, Folder 19)
    - Barrymore, Ethel - Roles (Box 107, Folder 20)
    - Barrymore, John C. - "Don Jean" (Box 107, Folder 21)
    - Barrymore, John C. - "My Dear Children" (Box 107, Folder 22)
    - Barrymore, John C. - Biography (Box 107, Folder 23)
    - Barrymore, John C. - Misc. (Box 107, Folder 24)
    - Barrymore, John C. - "Hamlet" (Box 107, Folder 25)
    - Barrymore, John C. - Critiques (Box 107, Folder 26)
    - Barrymore, John C. - Booklets (Box 107, Folder 27)
  - Performers (2)
    - Barrymore - Drew Families (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Bellamy, Ralph (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Bergner, Elizabeth (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Bergner, Elizabeth (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Bernhardt, Sarah - Biography (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Bernhardt, Sarah - Critiques (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Bernhardt, Sarah - Roles (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Bernhardt, Sarah - Commemorative Booklets (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Booth Family (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Booth, John Wilkes and Lincoln (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - Brynner, Yul (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - Burke, Billie (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - Campbell, Mrs. Patrick (Box 108, Folder 13)
    - Chaplin, Charles (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - Chevalier, Maurice (Box 108, Folder 15)
    - Cornell, Katharine - Biography (Box 108, Folder 16)
    - Cornell, Katharine - Biography (Box 108, Folder 17)
  - Performers (3)
    - Cornell, Katharine - Biography, misc. (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Cornell, Katharine - Biography, obits (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Cornell, Katharine - Critiques (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Cornell, Katharine - Roles (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Cornell, Katharine - Roles (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Cornell, Katharine - Roles (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Cornell, Katharine - Roles (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Cornell, Katharine - Roles (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Cornell, Katharine - Roles (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - Cornell, Katharine - Roles (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - Cornell, Katharine - Publication, Tour Materials (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - Cornell, Katharine - Francis Robinson's Publicity Research (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - Performers (4)
    - Cornell, Katharine - Playbills (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Cornell, Katharine - Souvenir Program (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Cornell, Katharine - Souvenir Program (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Cornell, Katharine - Souvenir Program (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Cornell, Katharine - Souvenir Program (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Coward, Noel - Biography (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Performers (5)
    - Coward, Noel - Critiques (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Coward, Noel - "Blithe Spirit" (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Coward, Noel - "Conversation Piece" (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Coward, Noel - "In Which We Serve" (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Coward, Noel - "Private Lives" (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Coward, Noel - Miscellaneous Roles (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Dietrich, Marlene (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Douglas, Melvyn (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Draper, Ruth (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Dunne, Ethne (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Duse, Eleanoro (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - Evans, Maurice - Biography (Box 111, Folder 12)
    - Evans, Maurice - Roles (Box 111, Folder 13)
    - Evans, Maurice - Roles (Box 111, Folder 14)
    - Evans, Maurice - Roles (Box 111, Folder 15)
    - Fairbanks, Douglas (Box 111, Folder 16)
    - Farmer, Frances (Box 111, Folder 17)
    - Fields, W. C. (Box 111, Folder 18)
    - Fiske, Minnie Maddern - Biography (Box 111, Folder 19)
    - Fiske, Minnie Maddern - Critiques (Box 111, Folder 20)
    - Fiske, Minnie Maddern - Roles (Box 111, Folder 21)
    - Fitzgerald, Barry (Box 111, Folder 22)
    - Forrest, Edwin (Box 111, Folder 23)
    - Garbo, Greta - Biography (Box 111, Folder 24)
    - Garbo, Greta - Roles (Box 111, Folder 25)
    - Gielgud, John - Roles (Box 111, Folder 26)
    - Gish, Lillian - Biography (Box 111, Folder 27)
    - Gish, Lillian - Critiques (Box 111, Folder 28)
    - Gish, Lillian - Roles (Box 111, Folder 29)
    - Gordon, Ruth (Box 111, Folder 30)
    - Hampden, Walter - Roles (Box 111, Folder 31)
    - Harrison, Richard B. (Box 111, Folder 32)
    - Hayes, Helen - Biography (Box 111, Folder 33)
    - Hayes, Helen - Critiques (Box 111, Folder 34)
    - Hayes, Helen - Roles (Box 111, Folder 35)
    - Hayes, Helen - Roles (Box 111, Folder 36)
    - Hayes, Helen - Roles (Box 111, Folder 37)
    - Hayes, Helen - Roles (Box 111, Folder 38)
    - Hayes, Helen - Roles (Box 111, Folder 39)
    - Hepburn, Katharine - Roles (Box 111, Folder 40)
    - Holliday, Judy (Box 111, Folder 41)
    - Howard, Leslie (Box 111, Folder 42)
    - Huston, Walter (Box 111, Folder 43)
    - Jolson, Al (Box 111, Folder 44)
    - Kaye, Danny (Box 111, Folder 45)
    - Lahr, Bert (Box 111, Folder 46)
  - Performers (6)
    - Lawrence, Gertrude - Biography (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Lawrence, Gertrude - Roles (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Le Blanc - maeternick (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Le Gallienne, Eva - Biography (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Le Gallienne, Eva - Roles (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Le Gallienne, Eva - Roles (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Le Gallienne, Eva - Roles (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Le Gallienne, Eva - Roles (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - Le Gallienne, Eva - Roles (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Le Gallienne, Eva - Roles (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - Le Gallienne, Eva - Commemorative Booklets (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - Leiber, Fritz (Box 112, Folder 12)
    - Lunt, Alfred and Lynn Fontanne - Biography (Box 112, Folder 13)
    - Lunt, Alfred and Lynn Fontanne - Critiques (Box 112, Folder 14)
    - Lunt, Alfred and Lynn Fontanne - Roles (Box 112, Folder 15)
    - Lunt, Alfred and Lynn Fontanne - Roles (Box 112, Folder 16)
    - Lunt, Alfred and Lynn Fontanne - Roles (Box 112, Folder 17)
    - Lunt, Alfred and Lynn Fontanne - Roles (Box 112, Folder 18)
    - Lunt, Alfred and Lynn Fontanne - Roles (Box 112, Folder 19)
    - Lunt, Alfred and Lynn Fontanne - Commemorative Booklets (Box 112, Folder 20)
    - Lynn, Diana (Box 112, Folder 21)
    - Mantell, Robert (Box 112, Folder 22)
    - March, Frederick (Box 112, Folder 23)
    - Marlowe, Julia (Box 112, Folder 24)
    - Martin, Mary (Box 112, Folder 25)
    - Massey, Raymond - Biography (Box 112, Folder 26)
    - Massey, Raymond - Roles (Box 112, Folder 27)
    - Meredith, Burgess - Biography (Box 112, Folder 28)
    - Meredith, Burgess - Roles (Box 112, Folder 29)
    - Morgan, Helen (Box 112, Folder 30)
    - Muni, Paul - Biography (Box 112, Folder 31)
    - Muni, Paul - Roles (Box 112, Folder 32)
    - Nazimova, Alla (Box 112, Folder 33)
    - Novarro, Ramon (Box 112, Folder 34)
    - Oliver-Leigh - Biography (Box 112, Folder 35)
    - Oliver-Leigh - Critiques (Box 112, Folder 36)
    - Oliver-Leigh - Roles (Box 112, Folder 37)
    - Oliver-Leigh - Roles (Box 112, Folder 38)
    - Oliver-Leigh - Roles (Box 112, Folder 39)
  - Performers (7)
    - Oliver-Leigh - Roles (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Oliver Laurence - Roles (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Oliver Laurence - Roles (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Skinner, Cornelia Otis - Biography (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Skinner, Cornelia Otis - Critiques (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Skinner, Cornelia Otis - Roles (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Skinner, Cornelia Otis - Roles (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Skinner, Cornelia Otis - Commemorative Booklets (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Skinner, Otis - Biography (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Skinner, Otis - Roles (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Sullavan, Margaret C. (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - Swanson, Gloria (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - Talmadge, Norma (Box 113, Folder 13)
    - Taylor, Laurette (Box 113, Folder 14)
    - Terry, Ellen - Biography (Box 113, Folder 15)
    - Terry, Ellen - Roles (Box 113, Folder 16)
    - Valentino, Rudolph - Biography (Box 113, Folder 17)
    - Valentino, Rudolph - Roles (Box 113, Folder 18)
    - Waters, Ethel (Box 113, Folder 19)
    - West, Mae (Box 113, Folder 20)
    - Performers (Box 113, Folder 21)
  - Performers (8)
    - Performers - Bill Robinson (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Performers - Katherine Dunham (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Performers - Bali (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Performers - China (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Performers - India (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Performers - Japan (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Performers - Mexico (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Performers - Philippines (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Performers - Spain (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Performers - Carmen Amaya (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - Performers - L'Argentinita (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Performers - L'Argentinita (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - Performers - Vincente Escudero (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - Performers - Carola Goya (Box 114, Folder 14)
    - Performers - Jose Greco (Box 114, Folder 15)
    - Performers - Rosario and Antonio (Box 114, Folder 16)
    - Performers - Shan-Kar, Vday (Box 114, Folder 17)
  - Theatre (1)
    - History - Performers (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - History - Productions (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - History - Miscellaneous (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - The Abbey Theatre Players (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - American National Theatre and Academy (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - The APA Repertory Company (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Barrault, Jean-Louis (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Cape Playhouse (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - General City Opera (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - Civic Light Opera (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - Covent Garden (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - D'Oyley Carte (Gilbert and Sullivan) (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - Empire (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - Theatre (2)
    - Ford's Theatre (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Tyrone Guthrie Theatre (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Los Angeles Civic Light Opera Association, Mohawk Drama Festival Muny Opera Association, Pesadena Community Playhouse (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Nashville Theatre (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - National Theatre (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Old Vic Company (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - The Players (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - The Playwrights' Company (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - The Repertory Theatre (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - Ryman Auditorium (Box 116, Folder 10)
    - Shakespeare Memorial Theatre (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Theatre (3)
    - Small Companies (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - St. Louis Municipal Opera (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Theatre Guild (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Nationalities - France (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Nationalities - China (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Nationalities - Great Britain (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Nationalities - Hungary (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Nationalities - Ireland (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Nationalities - Japan (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Nationalities - Russia (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Nationalities - Yiddish and German (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Theatre (4)
    - Style - The "Method" (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Movies (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Movies - People (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Musicals (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Puppets (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Vaudeville (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Theatre - the 1930's (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Theatre - the 1940's (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Theatre - the 1950's (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Theatre - the 1960's (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Theatre - the 1970's (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Abie's Irish Rose (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Barrens of Wimpole Street (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - Becky Sharp (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - Candida (Box 118, Folder 15)
    - Caesar and Cleopatra (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - Theatre (5)
    - The Cherry Orchard and Chu Chin Chow (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Cyrano (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Fiddler on the Roof (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Green Pastures (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Hello Dolly (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - House of Rothschild (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Hunchback of Notre Dame (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Madwoman of Chaillot (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - Major Barbara (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - Man and Superman (Box 119, Folder 10)